[{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980265079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":7896,"timeElapsed":23588},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980268480,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3400,"timeElapsed":26989},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980271307,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2826,"timeElapsed":29816},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980276749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":5441,"timeElapsed":35258},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980280962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":4212,"timeElapsed":39471},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980285393,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4430,"timeElapsed":43902},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980290771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":5376,"timeElapsed":49280},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980294825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4053,"timeElapsed":53334},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980301085,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"208","question":"Do you consider yourself more of a “cat person” or a “dog person”? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6259,"timeElapsed":59594},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980315331,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7376,"timeElapsed":73840},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980318399,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3067,"timeElapsed":76908},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980321648,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3248,"timeElapsed":80157},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980326150,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4501,"timeElapsed":84659},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980329079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2928,"timeElapsed":87588},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980333322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4242,"timeElapsed":91831},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980337240,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3917,"timeElapsed":95749},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980343408,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":6167,"timeElapsed":101917},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980346671,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"19","question":"If you knew that in one year you would die suddenly, would you change anything about the way you are now living? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3262,"timeElapsed":105180},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980359962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":11712,"timeElapsed":118471},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980362776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2813,"timeElapsed":121285},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980365533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2756,"timeElapsed":124042},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980370274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4740,"timeElapsed":128783},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980373847,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3572,"timeElapsed":132356},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980376913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3065,"timeElapsed":135422},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980380659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3745,"timeElapsed":139168},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980388456,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7796,"timeElapsed":146965},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980393565,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":5108,"timeElapsed":152074},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980397693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"91","question":"What physical feature of yours would a caricature artist blow out of proportion?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4127,"timeElapsed":156202},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980405429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":6117,"timeElapsed":163938},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980408055,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2625,"timeElapsed":166564},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980411153,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3098,"timeElapsed":169662},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980414479,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3325,"timeElapsed":172988},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980417886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3406,"timeElapsed":176394},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980421356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3469,"timeElapsed":179865},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980426668,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5311,"timeElapsed":185177},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980431009,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4340,"timeElapsed":189518},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980434339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"244","question":"Are you typically early for things or do you often run late? Has this ever gotten you into trouble or helped you out in some way?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3329,"timeElapsed":192848},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980441739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":5865,"timeElapsed":200248},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980444750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3010,"timeElapsed":203259},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980447959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3208,"timeElapsed":206468},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980453032,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5072,"timeElapsed":211541},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980460817,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":7783,"timeElapsed":219326},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980463346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2528,"timeElapsed":221855},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980465952,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2606,"timeElapsed":224461},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980468481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2528,"timeElapsed":226990},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980471053,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2571,"timeElapsed":229562},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980482500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":10070,"timeElapsed":241009},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980489364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":6863,"timeElapsed":247873},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980492019,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2654,"timeElapsed":250528},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980495074,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3054,"timeElapsed":253583},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980498508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3434,"timeElapsed":257017},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980501109,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2599,"timeElapsed":259618},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980504323,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3213,"timeElapsed":262832},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980507024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2700,"timeElapsed":265533},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980510582,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3557,"timeElapsed":269091},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980519211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4837,"timeElapsed":277720},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980522586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3374,"timeElapsed":281095},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980525330,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2743,"timeElapsed":283839},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980528250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2919,"timeElapsed":286759},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980530777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2526,"timeElapsed":289286},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980534055,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3278,"timeElapsed":292564},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980538906,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4850,"timeElapsed":297415},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980542126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3218,"timeElapsed":300635},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980544961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2834,"timeElapsed":303470},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980548500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3539,"timeElapsed":307009},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980556382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":6050,"timeElapsed":314891},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980559539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3156,"timeElapsed":318048},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980562538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2998,"timeElapsed":321047},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980565309,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2770,"timeElapsed":323818},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980567608,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2298,"timeElapsed":326117},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980570005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2396,"timeElapsed":328514},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980572711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2705,"timeElapsed":331220},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980575773,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3062,"timeElapsed":334282},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980578515,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2741,"timeElapsed":337024},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980583473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3404,"timeElapsed":341982},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980586619,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3145,"timeElapsed":345128},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980590539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3919,"timeElapsed":349048},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980593912,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3371,"timeElapsed":352421},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980597646,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3733,"timeElapsed":356155},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980601818,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4171,"timeElapsed":360327},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980604513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2694,"timeElapsed":363022},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980607298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2784,"timeElapsed":365807},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980610648,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3349,"timeElapsed":369157},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980616530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":4406,"timeElapsed":375039},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980619370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2840,"timeElapsed":377879},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980621852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2481,"timeElapsed":380361},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980625366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3513,"timeElapsed":383875},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980628536,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3169,"timeElapsed":387045},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980631489,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2952,"timeElapsed":389998},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980633966,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2476,"timeElapsed":392475},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980636644,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2678,"timeElapsed":395153},{"subjectID":"2ege463c9h","prolificID":"5611f6dd7ffc8a00058117e7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23d246709d0172ba49a","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980639906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3260,"timeElapsed":398414}]